(Leonard:)Well, yeah.
(Sheldon:)Wow.
(Sheldon:)How dare the university force me
to go back to string theory!
(Amy:)They just don't appreciate you.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, and on top of that,
Leonard has the audacity
(Sheldon:)to suggest that now
that he and Penny are engaged,
(Sheldon:)he may not want
to live with me anymore.
(Amy:)Here, I made you
some Strawberry Quik.
(Sheldon:)I have real problems here, Amy.
(Sheldon:)I can't be mollified with
a beverage designed for children.
(Sheldon:)Mm. Yummy.
(Raj:)You know,
this might work out for the best.
(Amy:)You're always complaining about
what a terrible roommate Leonard is.
(Amy:)Like how he turns up
the thermostat when you're not there.
(Sheldon:)Ugh. It's like
walking into the Amazon.
(Sheldon:)And not the good Amazon
with one-day shipping.
(Sheldon:)The awful one with birds and snakes.
(Amy:)You hate the sound of all
those keys on his key chain.
(Sheldon:)Four keys!
(Sheldon:)Who does he think he is, a warden?